{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"2900/60",
			"answer":"2900/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4904/95",
			"answer":"4904/95",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4182/55",
			"answer":"4182/55",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9096/30",
			"answer":"9096/30",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5962/83",
			"answer":"5962/83",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"132.7/0.44",
			"answer":"132.7/0.44",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"762.9/0.062",
			"answer":"762.9/0.062",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"15.41/7.3",
			"answer":"15.41/7.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.3143/56",
			"answer":"0.3143/56",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"28.22/60",
			"answer":"28.22/60",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}